<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">L'RCP va proseguita fino all'arrivo dei soccorsi avanzati (servizio di emergenza territoriale o team di emergenza intraospedaliera) che subentreranno. E' importante dare comunicazione a chi arriva di quanto fatto fino a quel momento consentendo così di procedere oltre senza dover ricominciare da capo.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Prosegui l'RCP fino all'arrivo del team di soccorso avanzato. Ricordati di comunicare quanto è avvenuto fino a quel momento.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Ricordati di dare consegne al team di soccorso avanzato.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="EmergencyArrivesOverdoseEvaluationCorrect" level="Novice">La valutazione è corretta.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="EmergencyArrivesOverdoseEvaluationWrong" level="Novice">La valutazione sulla stato di overdose è sbagliata. Non ti sei accorto che uno degli oggetti che hai rimosso all'inizio dello scenario era una siringa?</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">The CPR should be continued until advanced medical help arrives (such as an emergency services or hospital emergency team). It is important to inform them of what actions have been taken so far, allowing them to proceed without starting from the beginning.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Continue CPR until the arrival of advanced emergency services. Remember to communicate what has happened so far.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Remember to give instructions to the advanced rescue team.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="EmergencyArrivesOverdoseEvaluationCorrect" level="Novice">Your evaluation is correct.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="EmergencyArrivesOverdoseEvaluationWrong" level="Novice">Your evaluation of the overdose state is wrong. Didn't you notice the objects on the floor at the start of the procedure. There was a syringe on the ground.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
