<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Il paziente deve essere in posizione supina con le braccia lungo i fianchi. Muovi gli arti afferrando le sfere rosse in corrispondenza di polsi e caviglie e posizionali nel punto giusto come indicato dalle sfere blu. Quando l'arto è in posizione corretta la sfera da rossa diventerà verde. Inoltre, è necessario scoprire il torace della vittima, e qualora fossero presenti dei vestiti, questi vanno rimossi, eventualmente aiutandoti con l'uso di una forbice.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Il paziente deve essere in posizione supina con le braccia lungo i fianchi ed il torace libero.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Victim Alignment Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentCorrectLimbPositioned" level="Novice">Bene, hai correttamente posizionato {"LIMB":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentUserInfoPlural" level="Novice">Non hai correttamente allineato tutti gli arti. Ti mancano ancora i seguenti arti da posizionare: {"LIMB":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentUserInfoSingular" level="Novice">Non hai correttamente allineato tutti gli arti. Devi ancora posizionare {"LIMB":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentRemoveClothes" level="Novice">Adesso devi rimuovere i vestiti per avere libero accesso al petto del paziente. Use le forbici vicine a lui. Afferrale e portale vicinie al petto del paziente.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">Place the patient in a supine position with their arms by their sides. Move their limbs by grasping the red spheres at the wrists and ankles and positioning them correctly as indicated by the blue spheres. When the limb is in the correct position, the red sphere will turn green. Additionally, it is necessary to uncover the victim's chest, and if there are clothes, they should be removed, possibly with the help of scissors.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">The patient should be lying on their back with their arms along their sides and their chest exposed.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Victim Alignment Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentCorrectLimbPositioned" level="Novice">Good, you correctly placed the victim's {"LIMB":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentUserInfoPlural" level="Novice">You did not yet correctly aligned all limbs. There are still the following limbs to be placed in the correct place: {"LIMB":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentUserInfoSingular" level="Novice">You did not yet correctly aligned all limbs. There is still the LIMB to be placed in the correct place</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="VictimAlignmentRemoveClothes" level="Novice">Now you have to remove clothes in order to have clear access to the patient's chest. Use the scissors close to him. Grab them and bring them close to the patient's chest.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
