<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Usa la mano destra, posizionando indice e medio sul lato del collo rivolto a sè, per verificare la presenza di polso carotideo. Una mano virtuale blu ti indica come fare. La presenza o assenza di polso è indicata da un suono e da un'interfaccia grafica sul collo del paziente.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Usa la mano destra per identificare la presenza di polso.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Controlla la presenza di battito cardiaco.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulse" level="Novice">Il paziente ha polso? {CONFIRM="MICROSOFT":"Rispondi Yes o No.";"AZURE":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulseCorrect" level="Novice">La tua valutazione è corretta.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulseWrong" level="Novice">La tua valutazione del polso è sbagliata. Il paziente {PULSE-STATE="PULSE":"ha polso";"NO-PULSE":"non ha polso"}. La corretta valutazione del polso è necessaria per procedere correttamente con la procedura.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseCarotidHandPlaced" level="Novice">Ottimo. Mano correttamente posizionata. Adesso ascolta se senti il battito della vittima.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseUserInfo" level="Novice">Devi posizionare la mano come indicato dalla mano virtuale blu.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">Check the presence of the carotid pulse using your right hand, placing your index and middle finger on the side of the neck facing you. A blue virtual hand will show you how to do it. The presence or absence of the pulse is indicated by a sound and a graphical interface on the patient's neck.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Use your right hand to check for a pulse.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Check for pulse.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulse" level="Novice">Does the patient have pulse? {CONFIRM="MICROSOFT":"Answer Yes or No.";"AZURE":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulseCorrect" level="Novice">Your evaluation is correct.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseAssessPulseWrong" level="Novice">Your evaluation of the patient's pulse is wrong. The patient has {PULSE-STATE="PULSE":"pulse";"NO-PULSE":"no pulse"}. The correct evaluation of the pulse is necessary to understand how to proceed with the emergency procedure.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseCarotidHandPlaced" level="Novice">Great. Hand correctly positioned. Now listen if you can hear the victim's pulse.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckPulseUserInfo" level="Novice">You must position your hand like the blu virtual one.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
