<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Estendi il capo con la mano sinistra, avvicina l'orecchio alla bocca del paziente e guarda il torace in modo da osservarne il respiro. Una sfera blu indica il punto da raggiungere con la testa ed un'interfaccia grafica di aiuterà a contare il tempo di osservazione. Riempi tutta la barra circolare e poi rispondi alla domanda in base alla tua valutazione sullo stato di respiro del paziente.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Valuta lo stato di respiro del paziente, posizionando l'orecchio sulla bocca del paziente e osservandone il torace per la presenza di respiro.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Verifica la presenza di respiro.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreath" level="Novice">Pensi che il paziente stia respirando. {CONFIRM="MICROSOFT":"Rispondi Yes o No.";"AZURE":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreathCorrect" level="Novice">La tua valutazione del respiro è corretta.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreathWrong" level="Novice">La tua valutazione sul respiro è sbagliata. Il paziente {BREATHING-STATE="BREATHING":"sta respirando";"NOT-BREATHING":"non sta respirando"}. La corretta valutazione del respiro è necessaria per procedere correttamente con la procedura.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathUserInfoNotLooked" level="Novice">Non hai guardato il petto del pazientte per 5 secondi. Assicuratti di completare la barra di progressione circloare.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathUserInfoNotPositioned" level="Novice">Devi posizionare la testa correttamente sopra a quella del paziente. Usa la sfera blu come riferimento.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">Extend the head with your left hand, bring your ear close to the patient's mouth, and look at the chest to observe the breathing. A blue sphere indicates the point to reach with the head and a graphical interface will help you count the observation time. Fill the entire circular bar and then answer the question based on your assessment of the patient's breathing status.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Evaluate the patient's breathing status by positioning your ear near the patient's mouth and observing the chest for breathing.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Evaluate the presence of breath.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreath" level="Novice">Do you think the patient is breathing. {CONFIRM="MICROSOFT":"Answer Yes or No.";"AZURE":""}</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreathCorrect" level="Novice">Your evaluation is correct.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathAssessBreathWrong" level="Novice">Your evaluation of the breathing state of the patient is wrong. The patient is {BREATHING-STATE="BREATHING":"breathing";"NOT-BREATHING":"not breathing"}. The correct evaluation of the breathing state is necessary to understand how to proceed with the emergency procedure.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathUserInfoNotLooked" level="Novice">You did not look at the patient's chest for 5 seconds. Make sure to completely fill the round progress bar.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="CheckBreathUserInfoNotPositioned" level="Novice">You must position your head correctly over the patient's head. Look at the blue sphere as a reference.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
