<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Quando ci si trova di fronte ad un soggetto potenzialmente incosciente, per prima cosa bisogna valutare l'effettivo stato di coscienza, scuotendo con cautela le spalle del soggetto e chiedendo ad alta voce "Signore, tutto bene?". Se il paziente non risponde è necessario chiedere aiuto.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Se il soggetto è incosciente, chiama aiuto.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Consciousness Evaluation Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoNoSpeakNoShake" level="Novice">Devi avvicinarti al paziente, scuotere con cautela le spalle e chiedere ad alta voce se ti sente</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoNoSpeakShake" level="Novice">Sei vicino al paziente ma non l'hai chiamata abbastanza forte</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoSpeakNoShake" level="Novice">Hai chiamato il paziente ma non hai scosso le spalle</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">When faced with a potentially unconscious individual, the first thing to do is assess their level of consciousness by gently shaking their shoulders and loudly asking, "Sir, are you okay?" If the patient does not respond, it is necessary to ask for help.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">If the subject is unconscious, call for help.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Consciousness Evaluation Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoNoSpeakNoShake" level="Novice">You need to approach the patient, gently shake their shoulders, and loudly ask if they can hear you.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoNoSpeakShake" level="Novice">You are close to the patient but you did not call him loud enough</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="ConsciousnessEvaluationUserInfoSpeakNoShake" level="Novice">You called the patient but you did not shake his shoulders</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
