<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">A questo punto è necessario erogare la scarica. Per prima cosa, si interrompe il massaggio cardiaco e si fa sicurezza: l'utente al defibrillatore si occupa di allontanare se stesso, l'eventuale altro soccorritore e qualsiasi altra persona presente sulla scena urlando "via io, via voi, via tutt!". Attenzione! E' necessario allontanare anche qualsiasi eventuale fonte di ossigeno dal paziente. </description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Interrompi il massaggio cardiaco per erogare la scarica.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Interrompi il massaggio cardiaco per erogare la scarica.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsNoScreamLook" level="Novice">Ricordati di urlare ad alta voce ai presenti di allontanarsi</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsNoScreamNoLook" level="Novice">Ricordati di urlare ad alta voce ai presenti di allontanarsi. Poi, guardati intorno per controllare che nessuno tocchi il paziente</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsScreamNoLook" level="Novice">Ricordati di guardarti intorno per controllare che nessuno tocchi il paziente</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">At this point, it's necessary to deliver the shock. First, interrupt CPR and ensure safety by having the person using the defibrillator and anyone else nearby to step back and shout "Clear! Everyone clear!" Make sure to also remove any sources of oxygen from the patient.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Interrupt cardiac massage in order to discharge.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Interrupt cardiac massage in order to discharge.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsNoScreamLook" level="Novice">Remember to scream out loud to bystander to step away</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsNoScreamNoLook" level="Novice">Remember to scream out loud to bystander to step away. Then look around to check nobody is touching the patient</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="DefibrillatorSecurityProtocolSuggestionsScreamNoLook" level="Novice">Remember to look around to check nobody is touching the patient</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
