<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Per poter intraprendere le manovre di rianimazione è necessario posizionarsi in maniera corretta rispetto al paziente. In caso di presenza di un solo soccorritore, questi deve inginocchiarsi sul lato destro del paziente all'altezza delle spalle (ginocchio sinistro del soccorritore all'altezza della spalla destra del paziente). Se invece sono presenti due soccorritori, il primo si posiziona come nel caso di un solo soccorritore, mentre il secondo si deve inginocchiare  dietro la testa del paziente per gestire la ventilazione. Vedrai un avatar blu che ti illustra come posizionarti, mettiti di fronte a lui.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Posizionati sul lato destro del paziente. Se siete in due, uno si inginocchi dietro la testa. </description>
      <description level="Expert">Learner Positioning Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="LearnerPositioningLearnerInPlace" level="Novice">Ora sei posizionato correttamente.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="LearnerPositioningUserInfo" level="Novice">Posizionati di fronte all'avatar blu.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">In order to perform resuscitation maneuvers, it is necessary to position oneself correctly in relation to the patient. In case of only one rescuer, this person must kneel on the right side of the patient at shoulder height (left knee of the rescuer at the height of the patient's right shoulder). If there are two rescuers, the first one positions themselves as in the case of only one rescuer, while the second one kneels behind the patient's head to manage ventilation. You will see a blue avatar that shows you how to position yourself, stand in front of it.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Position yourself on the right side of the patient. If you are two, one kneel behind the head.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Learner Positioning Expert</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="LearnerPositioningLearnerInPlace" level="Novice">Now you are correctly positioned.</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="LearnerPositioningUserInfo" level="Novice">Position yourself in front of the blue avatar.</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
