<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node>
   <language value="ITA">
      <description level="Novice">Il paziente ha polso ma non presenta respiro. Mentre aspetti i soccorsi devi fare le seguenti operazioni. Somministra un respiro ogni 6 secondi e controlla il polso ogni 2 minuti. Questo è uno scenario particolare in cui il paziente potrebbe trovarsi in un'intossicazione da oppioidi. Questa può avvenire in soggetti che ne fanno uso a scopo voluttuario oppure in pazienti che li hanno in terapia cronica. In ambito extraospedaliero la possono suggerire segni clinici (pupille miotiche, bradipnea o assenza di respiro), lo scenario (presenza di siringhe sulla scena, segni di venipuntura) o gli astanti, specie se in possesso di informazioni sulla terapia in atto al domicilio. In ambiente ospedaliero, inoltre, consultare la cartella clinica e la scheda di terapia permette di ottenere informazioni importanti. Somministra il naloxone qualora ritenessi che il paziente è in overdose da opioidi. Se non hai il naloxone aspetta i soccorsi e comunicagli la tua valutazione.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">In prenza di paziente incosciente, con polso e assenza di respiro, ricordati che potrebbe trattarsi di un'intossicazione da oppioidi.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Ricordati delle possibilità di intossicazione da oppioidi.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="PulseNoBreathingSequenceCheckPulse" level="Novice">Controlla il polso del paziente</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="PulseNoBreathingSequenceDeliverBreath" level="Novice">Somministra respiro ogni 6 secondi</nodePhrase>
   </language>
   <language value="ENG">
      <description level="Novice">The patient has a pulse but is not breathing. While you wait for emergency services, you should perform the following actions: administer one breath every 6 seconds and check the pulse every 2 minutes. This is a specific scenario where the patient may be suffering from opioid intoxication, which can occur in individuals who use opioids recreationally or in patients undergoing chronic therapy. In a non-hospital setting, clinical signs (constricted pupils, bradypnea or lack of breathing), the scenario (presence of syringes on the scene, signs of venipuncture), or witnesses, especially if they have information about therapy at home, may suggest it. In a hospital setting, consulting the medical record and therapy card provides important information. Administer naloxone if you believe the patient is suffering from an opioid overdose. If you do not have naloxone, wait for emergency services and communicate your assessment.</description>
      <description level="Intermediate">Remember that an unconscious patient with a pulse but no breathing could be experiencing opioid intoxication.</description>
      <description level="Expert">Remember the possibility of opioid intoxication.</description>
      <details level="Novice"/>
      <nodePhrase clipId="PulseNoBreathingSequenceCheckPulse" level="Novice">Check the pulse of the patient</nodePhrase>
      <nodePhrase clipId="PulseNoBreathingSequenceDeliverBreath" level="Novice">Now administer breath every 6 seconds</nodePhrase>
   </language>
</node>
